<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>g15billboard</title>
    <link>http://g15billboard.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on g15billboard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 07:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://g15billboard.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why The Time Is Now To Join The Mobile Revolution</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2019/01/09/mobile_revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2019/01/09/mobile_revolution/</guid>
      <description>You have probably heard the phrase “Timing is everything.” For the success of a business or a product, this is especially true.
Launching the right product at the right time all but ensures success &amp;ndash; heck, even launching the wrong product at the right time will give the product a better-than-even chance for success. But the right product at the wrong time usually ends in failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BizTrends2019: Media trends for 2019</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2019/01/07/biztrend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 13:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2019/01/07/biztrend/</guid>
      <description>2019 is poised to be the year where the integration of artificial intelligence permeates across all facets of marketing. This includes delivering better customer experiences across brands, driving better media targeting and helping define real-time media ROI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice for a 24-hour pocket mobile plan</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2018/12/05/advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2018/12/05/advice/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you had only 24 hours to put together a passable mobile marketing plan. What mobile tactics would you prioritise over a day because they are such non-negotiables? There is, in fact, a lot one could do in a normal working day that stretched into the evening because of less than optimal mobile planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G will become the mainstream ecosystem by 2022</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2018/11/27/5g/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/blog/2018/11/27/5g/</guid>
      <description>A research report released by Ericsson has provided a perspective on how 5G can be realised in Africa. The Making 5G a reality for Africa report, which was conducted in collaboration with the Council for Scientific and Industrial Research (CSIR), reveals that 5G will become the mainstream ecosystem by 2022, and we can expect to see 5G start being deployed by global leading operators during 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://g15billboard.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://g15billboard.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>